{
    "id": "3820e317091743788491dc20d27d620e",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is a …..................... . Catholic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "devote",
                "devout"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb598ce8f650413c8f7cc8459e4a03d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has .....................… her life to helping the poor and the sick.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "devoted",
                "devouted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd0628975bb7428389375aef3052953f"
        },
        {
            "question": "God is very …..................... ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "graceful",
                "gracious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c69f04f5c82f4d19b2ba5ab7b132f9a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can eat carrots cooked or .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "row",
                "raw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bab1472a91d74e8cb4d8777d6115f273"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .....................….. in sports.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excels",
                "exciles"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c88edf9c47f4e1bb1f632c2f074b872"
        },
        {
            "question": "His good works need to be .....................….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "commended",
                "commented"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "381f5a2a7e59425399648324a080afa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother ..................... . the weeping child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "concealed",
                "consoled"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ccb1a4cb2cf4038a160994ae3319f40"
        },
        {
            "question": "English literature is full of ..................... to Greek and Latin authors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "illusions",
                "allusions"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "648bf65fe7b1436d8054e5210c43c5f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though he is sixteen, he is very .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "childlike",
                "childish"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5eec8784f3e44519a34b812c7f30bac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was impressed by her .....................…… simplicity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "childlike",
                "childish"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3943afa4585f41548f93849113402d6b"
        }
    ]
}